This right here, we should call her Attorney General Patricia James because the pettiness
and the diligence is just mwah. So the New York Attorney General is now questioning the
qualifications of the company backing Trump's $175 million bond, which he posted last week
to safeguard his assets and prevent property seizure. Knight specialty insurance companies
attempt to post the bond has its obstacles because the big question is, can they actually
produce the cash on hand? Now, if they fail to provide the bond, New York Attorney General
Letitia Petitia James could proceed with enforcement actions on Trump's properties.
Like I'm talking like chaining the doors. It's a wrap. It's giving Al Capone like, okay,
we can't get you on these murders, but we're going to get you on this tax evasion. Like
we're going to get you. I'm leaving here with something. I'm leaving here with something.
Since Trump could end up like Al Capone, here's what a newsreel would sound like if he got caught
in the 1940s. In a draw-dropping twist straight out of a gangster flick, the notorious bigwig
Donald the Dumpster has finally been cuffed and stuffed by none other than the fearless dame
Letitia Elliott Ness James. Reports suggest that Trump's empire was as shaky as his hairpiece,
built on a foundation of funny money. Looks like his time strutting around like a big shot
is over. And now he's just another canary singing in the clink.
We are, we are, we are.